Guide to the Fred Chappell Papers, 1944-2019 and undated RL.00213
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accessions, 1993-2018
  - Accession (2018-0109), 1950s-2018
    - North Carolina Poetry Society, 2017 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 2)
      Contains copy of publication: Witness: Appalachia to Hatteras
    - Emory and Henry College: Fred Chappell Festival, 2017 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 2)
    - Dunham Literary Inc. royalties, correspondence, 2017-2018 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 2)
    - Canton (NC) public school materials for Fred Chappell, 1940s-1954 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 2)
    - Duke University materials, 1961 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 2)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters ceremonial, 1968 May 28 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 2)
    - North Carolina Literary and Historical Association roster, etc., 1973 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 2)
    - North Caroliniana Society publications, 2017 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 2)
    - Ma Famille Inoubliable (I am One of You Forever, French edition), 2018 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 3)
    - Foreword by Chappell to The Ultimate Actualist Convention, 2017 (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 3)
    - Family letters, 1960s-1980s; 2 folders (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 3)
      Letters, postcards, and clippings largely addressed to Chappell's parents, sent by him and his siblings.
    - Incoming letters and correspondence, 2017; 9 folders (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 3)
    - Incoming letters and correspondence, 2018; 5 folders (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 4)
    - Outgoing correspondence, 2017 May-2018 July; 4 folders (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 4)
    - Stuart Wright to Susan Chappell correspondence, 2000s and undated; 2 folders (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 4)
    - Clippings re: Fred Chappell, 1960s-1980s; 4 folders (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 4)
      Reviews, publication and event press, profiles and news coverage of Chappell's activities.
    - Events featuring Fred Chappell or attended by Fred Chappell, 1960s-1980s, 2018; 2 folders (Box Acc. 18/109: Box 4)
  - Accession (2019-0087), 1950s-2019
    Unsorted and unprocessed addition, including correspondence, manuscript drafts, and presentataion copies of books.
    - Correspondence, manuscript drafts, and presentation copies of published books. (Box Box Acc. 19-087: Box 1-5)